Sakura-chan, it’s been a while!
さくらちゃん、久しぶり!
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
How have you been lately?
最近元気してた?
Dizzy.
ぼちぼち
I see.
そうか
You've come to a beautiful place.
綺麗なとこ来たね
Amazing, beautiful.
すごい、綺麗
What have you been up to lately?
最近何してたの?
Studying...
勉強が...
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
It's been a while.
久しぶりに
I'm glad that it came naturally.
自然と振られてよかった
The atmosphere feels good.
空気気持ちよな
Because it feels good.
気持ちいいから
There's not a cloud in the sky today.
雲一つないよ、今日は
Are you feeling stressed lately?
最近ストレス溜まってるの?
It's accumulating.
溜まってる
After all, studying is hard.
や っぱ勉強が大変
Studying...I don't like it.
勉強...嫌だ
You look like you're smart.
頭良さそうな顔してるじゃん
Aren't you smart?
頭良くないの?
I see.
そうか
I feel negative here.
マイナスよく感じるな、ここね
Do you have any plans to play with friends?
友達と遊ぶ予定とかないの?
Recently.
最近は
Are you busy?
忙しいの?
Friends too.
友達も
Everyone is studying.
みんな勉強してるね
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Are there many serious girls around Sakura-chan?
さあくらちゃんの周り、真面目な子は多いのかな?
結構
Isn't there such a thing as a delinquent?
不良みたいなのいないの?
not present.
いない
He's not there.
いないんだ
It’s been a while
久しぶ
Are you a little nervous?
り、 ちょっと緊張する?
I'm a little nervous.
ちょっと緊張する
Let's walk around for a bit, then.
ちょっとそこらへん歩こう、そしたら
Try walking over there.
歩いてみてよ、あっちに
Sakura-chan, look at this.
さあくらちゃん見てこれ
That's amazing.
すごいぞ
Lots of ducks.
アヒルがいっぱい
Peace.
ピースして
There seem to be a lot of them.
いっぱいいるな、なんか
There are a lot of them.
い っぱいいる
cute.
かわいい
But this is where you ride.
しかしあなた乗るのはこっちです
It's just a normal guy.
普通のやつだろ
A little duck.
アヒルはちょっとね
Because it's a weekday.
平日だから
It's a cut off.
端切りです
Sakura-chan.
さあくらちゃん
yes.
はい
copper?
どう?
On this water?
この水の上?
Doesn't it shake a lot?
めっちゃ揺れない?
Super shaky.
超揺らい
According to the clerk earlier, there is one attached.
さっきの店員さんによると 添付したやつがいる
How about a boat date?
ボートデートどうですか?
It was my first time riding one, so it was amazing.
初めて乗ったから、すごい
It's downright fun.
地味に楽しいな
It's fun and feels good.
楽しいし、気持ちいい
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Sometimes it's like this,
たまにはこういうさ、
How many hours a day do you study?
一 日何時間くらい勉強してるの?
But I keep looking at my smartphone, so I have to stop using it as much as possible.
でもスマホ見ちゃうから、 スマホなるべくやめないといけない
What, what are you looking at on your smartphone?
え、スマホで何見るんだよ?
TikTok
Is there someone you like?
好きな人いるの?
On TikTok.
TikTokで
I don't have this person, but I have a lot of things from various people.
この人っていうのはないけど、 いろんな人のものをいっぱい
Look.
見て
fun?
楽 しい?
TikTok
fun.
楽しい
1 hour before I knew it.
気づいたら1時間
You slack off so much.
すげーサボるじゃん
I was worried that I was going to crash into this rock right now.
今この岩に激突しそうで焦ってた
It's coming to the other side.
反対側まで来ちゃってる
Do you want to go back a little?
少し戻りますか?
But you look cute today too.
でも今日も可愛いね
She looks like an idol, really.
アイドルみたいじゃん、本当に
I'm embarrassed.
照れちゃう
I'm glad I did it.
やれよよかったの
It's not too late now.
今からでも遅くないぞ
Really?
本当に?
Let's apply.
応募しよう
Are you going to do an idol project?
アイドル企画やっちゃう?
You don't have to study.
勉強しなくていいじゃん
勉強しなくていい
Become an idol and make everyone smile,
アイドルになってみんなを笑顔にして、
I'm happy that I got it from that video.
その動画で貰ってハッピーじゃん
surely.
確かに
She will make her idol debut next year.
来年アイドルデビューだな
Then.
そ したらね
Your casual clothes look cute today too.
今日は私服も可愛いね
thank you.
ありがとう
Favorite clothes?
お気に入りの服?
that.
それ
favorite
お気に入
the law of nature.
り
Flower pattern?
花 柄?
that.
それ
Floral pattern.
花柄
Sagra-chan looks good on you.
サグラちゃん似合ってるね
happy.
嬉しい
Don't you buy expensive branded clothes?
高いブランドの服買わないの?
Have you never bought one?
買ったことない?
Not much.
あんまり
I've never bought one.
買ったことない
My uncle bought it this time.
今度おじさん買ったんやよ
Really?
本当に?
Yay!
やったー
Don't lose your heart.
心が無になるな
That place.
その場所
I'm getting hungry.
お腹すいてくるわ
Did you eat anything today?
今日何か食べた?
Don't eat it.
食べてねぇじゃん
I haven't eaten.
食べてない
Just cream.
クリームとかだけ
You'll lose weight.
痩せちゃうね
Then.
そ したら
I'm really hungry.
めっちゃお腹すいた
Suita?
すいた?
It's okay to eat something.
少し何か食ってもいいね
Anyway, I'll be back in a little while.
とりあえずもうちょっとしたら戻るか
Then.
そしたら
Chiken is so cute.
チケン可愛いな
There are toys.
おもちゃある
Hello.
こんにちは
Sakura-chan has arrived.
さくらちゃん来ちゃったね
Ryoka.
りょうか
beautiful.
きれい
It's spacious and nice.
広くていいね
How was it at the beginning?
さっき冒頭どうだった?
it was fun.
楽しかった
It was my first experience.
初めての経験だったな
And Sakura-chan.
そしてさくらちゃん
You look really good in a yukata.
浴衣がめちゃめちゃ似合いますねあなた
copper?
どう?
See for yourself.
自分で見て
Isn't it cute?
可愛くない?
Nice hair.
いい毛が
But it suits you.
でも似合ってるよ
You put it in a ponytail.
ポニーテールにしたね
It’s been a while since I saw Ryokan-kun like this?
こういうりょうかんくんの久しぶり?
It's been a long time.
すごい久しぶり
That's right.
そうなんだ
Why don't you ask a man to take you there?
男の人に連れて行ってもらってしないの?
I don't.
しないの
You'll be invited.
誘われるでしょ
Let's go on a trip.
旅行行こうよって
Liar.
うそつけ
Really?
本当に?
Really.
本当に
You look cute today too.
今日も可愛いね
Do you like hot springs?
温泉とか好き?
Sakura-chan.
さくらちゃんは
I like hot springs.
温泉好き
I like it.
好きだな
Have you ever been to Hakone?
箱根とか行ったことある?
A long time ago.
すごい前に
it was fun?
楽しかった?
Isn't it fun to travel with just your female friends?
女友達だけで旅行しても楽しいんじゃない?
Do you not go often?
あんまり行かない?
It was fun, right?
楽しかったでしょ?
I like the yukata look.
浴衣姿いいね
It's fresh.
新鮮で
It looks great on you.
すごい似合ってるよ
Try standing up.
立ってみて
It's true.
ほ んとだ
Sakura-chan is small so she's doing her best.
さくらちゃん小さいからそう頑張ってるね
How tall is the boss?
身長何ボスだっけ?
148cm
About 8cm?
8cmくらい?
It's small today too.
今日も小さいね
Turn around.
後ろ向いて
Looks like someone who works at a medical facility like this.
こういう医療館で働いてる子いそう
Part-time job.
アルバイトで
Look here.
こっち見てみ
Today we have a surprise for cute Sakura-chan.
今日はかわいいさくらちゃんにサプライズがあります
A new character you meet for the first time.
初対面の新キャラ
Taro-chan is here.
太郎ちゃんがいるよ
Kuro-chan and Taro-chan.
黒ちゃんと太郎ちゃん
I mean, I don't think it's a threesome.
つまり、3Pって思わないけど
With two doujinshi, it doesn't end up like that, right?
同人2人とさ、そういう風になってこないでしょ?
Are you excited?
ドキドキする?
fun?
楽しみ?
Kuro-chan, come here.
黒ちゃん、こっち来
hand.
て
It's been a while.
お 久しぶりだね
Taro-chan, come here next time.
太郎ちゃん、今度こっち
Please come next to me.
横に来てもらって
copper?
どう?
Taro-chan is huge, and the height difference is amazing.
太郎ちゃんでっかくてさ、 身長の差もすごいね
What about tall men?
背高い男の人はどうよ?
like.
好き
Do you like it better than lower?
低いより好き?
Because I'm low.
自分が低いから
I see.
なるほどね
Kuro-chan, you have to do your best.
黒ちゃん、頑張らないとな
This cute Sakura-chan.
このかわいいさくらちゃんのさ
Let's take a look at the body one by one.
体ちょっとずつ見ていこうか
Take it off, Kuro-chan.
帯外してみよ、黒ちゃん
What a beautiful body.
すげえ綺麗な体
Taro-chan, I've never seen you before.
太郎ちゃん、 見たことないもんね、
Sakura-chan's.
さくらちゃんのね
copper?
どう?
This style.
このスタイル
It's so constricted and erotic.
めっちゃくびれててエロいわ
Look behind you.
後ろを向いてごらん
It's loli loli.
ロリロリだね
Sakura-chan, dig into your pants yourself.
さくらちゃん、自分でパンツから食い込まして
Turn to me and see only my face.
こっち向いてみ、顔だけ
Has the number of experience yen increased since then?
あれから経験円数増えた?
It won't change.
変わんない
変わんないんだ
It's so beautiful.
すごい綺麗だよ
Taro-chan, please chew on Sakura-chan's cheek.
太郎ちゃん、 さくらちゃんのほっぽに チューしてごらん
copper?
どう?
This 18-year-old has perfect skin.
この18歳の ピチピチの肌は
Kuro-chan, look between them.
黒ちゃん、はさんでごらん、
this.
これ
Two perverts and such a cute girl.
変 態二人にこんな 可愛い子が
Also try chewing on your neck and ears.
首とか、耳とかにもチューしてごらん
Sakura-chan, this is amazing.
さくらちゃん、 すごいね、これ
It's a strange feeling.
不思議な感じだね
first time.
初めて
Sakura-chan, you smell so good.
さくらちゃん、 いい匂いするで
Sho.
しょ
Kuro-chan, please chew it in your mouth.
黒 ちゃん、口にチューしてごら
yeah.
ん
Swallow one yen, Kuro-chan.
一 つ円飲み込んで、黒ちゃん
You look so naughty, Sakura.
すごいエッチな顔するね、 さくら
Chan.
ちゃん
Kuro-chan, it's tongue-in-cheek.
黒 ちゃん、ベロだし
Kuro-chan is tongue-tied.
黒ちゃん、ベロだし
It's tongue-in-cheek, Kuro-chan.
ベロだし、黒ちゃん
Suck on that.
それ吸ってごらん
Both of them are very licking, and they lick each other's licks.
二人ともベロベロやつだし、 ベロベロ舐め合って
Kuro-chan, take the blazer.
黒ちゃん、ブライザー取ってみ
You have a really beautiful body.
ほんと綺麗な体してるね
She's young, cute, and awesome.
若くて、可愛くて、最高だね
Dola-chan.
だろちゃん
Make it into breasts.
おっぱいにする
Look at your face.
顔をずんでみ
soft?
柔らかい?
Try chewing on your nipples.
乳首にチューしてごらん
Do Sakura-chan's breasts.
どうさくらちゃんのおっぱい
Kura-chan, Chu.
くらちゃん、チュー
Let me rub your nipples.
乳首ビンビンにたたしてあげて
This one stands up really well.
すっごい立ってんじゃん、これ
Honestly, Chuu.
ほんとだろちゃん、チュー
Kuro-chan, please lick my breasts.
黒ちゃん、おっぱい舐めてよ
Erotic licking.
エロい舐め方
It's a bummer, you see.
ちくりビンビンだよ、ほら
Dora-chan, suck it as hard as you can.
だろちゃん、思いっきり吸ってみ
Vero.
ベロ
Can I lick it all into my mouth?
全部口に舐めていい?
It's delicious.
おいしいじゃん
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
Take off your pants, that's it.
パンツ脱がしちゃえ、それ
I'm facing backwards.
そんま後ろ向いてる
Stick your butt out here.
お尻、こっち突き出してみ
So, turn your face towards me.
で、顔こっち向いて
It's an angel.
天使だね
It's so beautiful, look.
すーごい綺麗だよ、ほら
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Put one foot on the bed.
ベッドに片足を向いてごらん
Erotic pussy.
エロいマンコ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's a great match.
すーごい一致だよ
Try spreading your arms yourself.
自分で手を広げてごらん
The pussy of an eight year old is so erotic.
中八歳のマンコ、エロいね
Get on all fours on top of this.
この上、四つんまいになってごら
yeah.
ん
It's a really beautiful body
本当 に綺麗な体だ
hey.
ね
Erotic.
エ ロい
beautiful face.
綺麗な顔
Look at your cute face.
可愛い顔、こっち向いて
Open your legs.
足を持って開く
Show me your pussy.
おマンコ、見せつけて
Soooo cute.
すーごい可愛い
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
恥ずかしい
Kuro-chan, I want to raise this as high as I can.
黒ちゃん、この思いっきり上げたいね
Show me your pink pussy.
ピンクのマンコ、見せつけてごらん
It's so humid.
すーごい湿ってる
Sakura-chan, why are you wet?
サクラちゃん、なんで濡れてんの?
I felt a little binamed.
ちょっとバイナメられて感じたの
Sakura is a pervert.
変態者のサクラじゃん
Pink, so beautiful.
ピンク、すーごい綺麗
The butt hole.
お尻の穴のほう
Naughty hole.
エッチな穴
Look this way next time.
今度こっち向いて
Look at it in an M-shape.
M字になってごら
yeah.
ん
Facing the chestnut skin.
栗 の皮向いて
You like chestnut tresses without touching them, right?
栗トレス触らんの好きでしょ?
like?
好 き?
Now go to the bed and lean against the wall.
じゃあベッドのほうに行って、壁に寄っかかってみて
So lean back and stick your butt out as hard as you can.
それで後ろに寄っかかって、お尻を思いっきり突き出す
Erotic.
エロ
Open your pussy yourself.
自分でおまんこ開いて
I can see inside your nose.
鼻の中まで見えるよ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
My pussy is so wet.
おまんこすごい濡れてる
That's a naughty pussy.
エッチなまんこだね
I'm excited to see it.
見られて興奮するんだ
Try touching a chestnut yourself.
自分で栗触ってごらん
I always touch my place when I masturbate.
オナインするときいつもトコ触るの
Let me show you.
見せてごらん
Chestnut is standing up as hard as she can.
栗思いっきり立ってんじゃんこれ
You know for yourself.
分かるでしょ自分で
Chew it lightly, Kuri-chan.
栗ちゃん、軽くチューしてごらん
Try eating all the buns.
まんじゅう全部食べてみて
Kuri-chan, when she masturbates, she thrusts it all in.
栗ちゃん、オナインしたら全部突っ込む
delicious?
美味しい?
Yeah, it's delicious.
うん、美味しい
Taro-chan, go next door.
太郎ちゃん、隣行って
Chew it.
チューしてごらん
That's naughty.
エッチだね
I got licked both top and bottom.
上も下も舐められちゃって
Isn't it great?
すごい良くない?
It's very egotistical.
めっちゃエゴいじゃん
Chestnut-chan, I'm smoking all the chestnuts.
栗ちゃん、栗全部吸ってる
I put it all in my mouth.
口の中いっぱい入れてる
Give me a ring.
リンビンしてあげて
Even Chikubi stood up like that.
チクビもそんな立てちゃって
It's really naughty.
エッチだね本当に
Kuri-chan, I want to lick your asshole too.
栗ちゃん、ケツ穴も舐めたい
Have a bun.
まんじゅうして
Taro-chan, Chuu.
太郎ちゃん、チュー
Kuri-chan, I want to lick everything.
栗ちゃん、全部舐めたい
Drink all the manju.
まんじゅう全部飲み干して
Taro-chan also has more lips.
太郎ちゃんも唇もっと
Chew to your heart's content.
思いっきりチューしてごらん
Even the asshole.
ケツ穴もくらい
Open more.
もっと開いて
Okay.
いいよ
Kuri-chan, open your pussy as wide as you can.
栗ちゃん、 おまんこ思いっきり開いてみして
That's amazing.
すごいよ
I can see the deepest part.
一番奥まで見えてる
Try peeling the chestnuts too.
栗も剥いてごらん
Make it lower than your nose.
鼻より低くして
Just sit here.
ここ座ってごらん
Both of us.
二人とも
I feel like I'm struggling with both today.
なんか、今日 二つともがいがある
What is this?
なんでしょうか、これは
It's chin chin.
チンチンだね
The smell comes from both of my pants.
パンツの上からどっちも匂いが入ってくる
Touch both with your hands.
両方手で触って
It's been a long time since I had chin chin.
久しぶりにチンチンが
Pull up your pants.
パンツ上げてみ
That's amazing.
すごいね
I read them at the same time.
同時に読みちゃったね
It's Kuri-chan's stick.
栗ちゃんの棒棒だよ
It's like two types of dicks.
2種類のタイプのチンコって感じ
It makes me laugh so much.
めっちゃ笑うじゃん
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Well, grab both of them.
じゃあ、二つともそれ握って
That's amazing.
すごいね
With such a pure face.
こんなピュアな顔して
I'm thinking of seeing Chin Chin.
チンチン見ようと思っちゃってるの
Look at Chin Chin.
チンチン見てみ
hard?
硬い?
Both of you put it on that hard dick face.
二人ともその硬いチンチン顔につけてみて
Rub it in more.
もっといっぱいこすりつけて
I'm going to lick it.
ぺちぺちしちゃう
I'll just stick to my dick.
チンコだけにしちゃうよ
I also put a lot on my lips.
唇にもいっぱい付けていく
I'll put them all on.
全部つけていく
Chew one at a time.
片方ずつチューしてくれ
Bever.
ベバーして
I'll lick that pleasant place behind there.
そこの裏の気持ちいいとこ いっぱい舐めてあげる
Hold it here with your finger.
指でこっち持って
Put it all in your mouth.
口の中全部入れて
Don't talk a lot.
いっぱい喋りつけな
Make yourself feel good.
いっぱい気持ちよくしてみな
Put both of them in your mouth.
二つとも口の中入れて
Everything is good.
全部いいな
Try putting both in your mouth.
口の中にどっちも入れてごらん
It's full of dicks.
チンチンでいっぱいだよ
Look, in your mouth.
ほ ら、口の中に
it hurts?
痛い?
Isn't it painful?
苦しいでしょ?
Don't let go.
離しちゃダメ
Just keep licking it.
そのままペロペロして
Swallow it all the way, chinchi
一番奥まで飲み込んで、チンチ
hmm.
ン
It's big.
大 きいね
Also the opposite Chin Chin.
反対のチンチンも
it hurts?
痛い?
It's bitter, head.
苦いじゃん、頭
I'll follow you more.
もっとついちゃう
That's tough, Chin Chin.
固いだろ、チンチン
One hand held the other hand's chin chin.
片っぽで手反対のチンチン持ってて
Put the last two in your mouth.
最後2つの口入れて
Swallow it all, Chinch.
もっと全部飲み込んで、チンチ
hmm.
ン
It's almost painful.
苦 しいぐらい
Drink a lot.
いっぱい飲んで
Please both of you sit down.
二人ともお座ってごらん
Try licking it once.
一回舐めてごらん
It's spitting.
ツバベったり
Coming up from below.
下からつきあがり
A soaking cock.
ビショビショなチンチン
There are two big ones.
2つも大きいのあるね
Try swishing with both.
両方でシュシュしてごらん
Take both of them and get them wet.
2つともツバベいっぱい持って濡らして
Let Beth be Beth.
ベートをベートにしてあげな
How are you both?
2人ともどう?
this.
これ
Well then, we're both Sakurashi this time.
じゃあ、2人とも今度はサクラシのさ
Shall I attack you?
よく襲っちゃおうか
You licked a lot of cock.
いっぱいチンチン舐めたね
Can I use Sakurashi this time?
今度はサクラシにしめていい?
Look at the neckline there.
そこにネックルがあってごらん
Hold it on top like this.
こうやって上にかかえてて
Try licking my armpits.
脇舐めてごらん
Does it taste like sweat?
汗の味する?
Lick it all.
全部舐めて
I've already come to my senses.
もう内首立ってきたよ
Try licking my boobs too.
おっぱいも舐めてごらん
Can I lick all the places I like?
好きなところいっぱい舐めていい?
Can I lick it a lot?
いっぱいぺろぺろしていい?
Can I have a tube or something?
チューブとかもしちゃっていい?
I was licked by so many amazing things.
すごいのいっぱい舐められてね
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ
Make yourself feel good.
いっぱい気持ちよくしてごらん
You can lick it all.
全部舐めていいよ
Try putting it all you can.
思いっきり入れてごらん
Open your pussy.
おまんこ開いてみて
I'm starting to feel like a chestnut.
栗ビンビンになってきたよ
Try putting your finger in there too.
指も入れてごらん
tits.
おっぱい
Look at your face.
顔こっち見てごらん
Your pussy is tight, isn't it?
おまんこきついでしょこれ
Give me your feet like this.
足こうやってあげて
Do the same for the other leg.
反対の方の足もこうやって
Look, my neck is throbbing too.
首もビンビンだよほら
Does your pussy feel good?
おまんこ気持ちいい?
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Can I use it comfortably?
気持ちよく使っていい?
Try raising it.
上 げてみして
You look so sexy right now.
すごいエロい顔してるよ今
toward the hole.
穴の方に
I was licking everything.
全部舐めてた
towards the butt.
お尻の方に
It's sticky and sticky.
マンジュルでベタベタだよ
I'm going to put it inside Porto earlier.
さっきポルト中まで入れちゃう
This hole is so tight.
きっついよこの穴
Lick the chestnut.
栗舐めて
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Can you see me trembling inside your pussy?
おまんこの中で震えてるのわかる?
It's stuck in my hand.
手に刺さってるよほら
Try moving your hands too?
手も動かしてみ?
Take it slow.
ゆっくりね
You swallowed such a tiny mango.
こんなちっちゃいマンゴー飲み込んじゃったね
Please pull it out slowly.
ゆっくり抜いてごらん
This is tough.
きっついねこれ
Look at Chiban as he gets fatter.
チバンを太れてごらん
With a bang.
パンパンでね
Take it out.
抜いてごらん
Look at your nose.
鼻見して
Sakura-chan, try it yourself.
桜ちゃん自分でやってごらん
Both of them have their legs pinned down.
二人は足を押さえてされてる
Her pussy is open
おまんこ開きなが
and others.
ら
A white manjul appears.
白 いマンジュル出てるよ
Naughty juice.
エッチな汁
Tao-chan, put your finger in it.
タオちゃん指入れてみ
Please help me
手伝ってもらって
good?
いい?
A lot of juice comes out inside your pussy.
お まんこの中で汁いっぱい出てくるね
Kuma-chan, lick your armpits.
くまちゃん脇舐めて
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
You can't run away.
逃げちゃダメだからね
Just be patient.
我慢だよ
Tell me what you say.
何を言っちゃってくれ
If it's a tight hole.
キッツい穴ならね
Is this how you got your big penis?
こうやってでっかいチンチャ入んの?
Do your best and be patient.
頑張って我慢して
Are you going?
行っちゃうの?
Never look.
決してごらん
Everyone's watching, hey.
みんな見てるよ、オラ
Have you gone?
行っちゃったの?
Let's try it again.
もう一度やってみましょう
Please let me know more when you go further.
も っと行くときにいっぱい教えてください
That's amazing, your child.
すごいね、おまえの子
Give me a good lick
しっくり舐めてあげて
please.
ください
please show me.
見 せてください
Please spread your nose and show me.
鼻を広げて見せてください
I went there twice.
2回も行ってしまいました
Keep it low.
低くしてください
Please use something higher.
もっと高いものを使ってください
Please bend your legs.
足を曲げてください
You can just see it through the hole.
穴で見えるくらいです
It's slow.
ゆ っくりです
It's really absorbing.
す げえ吸い付いています
I got something thick inside.
太いものが入ってしまいました
Mr. Towel, please be careful.
タオルさん、注意してください
Mr. Towel, don't push it too hard.
タオルさん、それを強くしないで
please.
ください
Please do it once every night.
1回 寝たまにしてください
Become four cases.
4つの場合になってください
Please stick to it.
プリッと付き出してください
Mr. Tao Lu, please fill this up.
タ オ ル さん、これにいっぱい入れてください
hero
ヘロ
is.
です
It really hits home.
す げえぶっ刺さっています
Please spread your legs wider.
もっと足を広げてください
Mr. Towel, please lick my hole.
タオルさん、穴を舐めてください
Make the hole you removed.
抜いた穴にしてください
There's something thick in there.
太いものが入っています
Mr. Towel, please lick it as much as possible.
タオルさん、いっぱい舐めてください
Now please bully the two of them.
今度は2人をイジメしてください
Please sleep two people.
2人寝てください
It's the opposite.
逆です
It's Sakura.
サクラです
two people together
2人くっついて
please.
ください
Please make me feel good again.
また 気持ちよくしてください
Please stand up like chubo chubo.
チューボーチューボーと立ててください
It looks comfortable.
気持ちよさそうです
Please suck it all.
しゃぶりつくしてください
My penis has gotten bigger.
ちんちんが大きくなりました
cute face
かわいい顔
is.
です
The second one is also big.
2つ 目も大きいです
How do you feel?
どんな気がしますか?
The second one is also big.
2つ目も大きいです
Huge penis
でっかいちんちん
is.
です
It's the biggest.
一 番大きいです
Are you in pain?
苦しいですか?
It's huge.
でっかいです
in the first place
そもそも
is.
です
Can you please lick my baby?
お 前の子いっぱい舐めてもらえない?
Does it feel good to be licked?
舐められて気持ちいい?
The bottom penis is also nice.
下のちんちんもいいです
Please make both of you feel comfortable.
どっちも気持ちよくしてください
Please take turns licking your favorite child.
交互に好きな子を舐めてください
Let's try both.
両方とも食わえてみよう
Lots of tongue
ベロを使っていっぱい
is.
です
Put both your shoulders and your mouth.
肩 にも両方口の中に入れて
Compare your face and size.
自分の顔とサイズを比べてみましょう
Should I be under Kuro-chan?
黒ちゃん下になろうか
Turn your head this way.
頭をこっち向き
Now, Kuro-chan, turn this way too.
さあ、黒ちゃんもこっち向き
Deeper.
もっと奥まで
Squeeze the bottom too.
下もしこしこして
Isn't it delicious?
ちんちんおいしいでしょう?
Kuro-chan, thrust further down.
黒ちゃんもっと下に突っ込んで
Let's throw in Kuro-chan too.
黒ちゃんもぶち込もうか
Turn your head this way.
頭をこっち向き
Please bring your own.
自分でチンチン持って入れてください
I swallowed hard.
すごい飲み込んだ
Looks like naughty.
エッチのっぽい
So cute.
すごい可愛い
Please move on your own.
自分で動いてください
Hold your hips fully.
腰をいっぱい持ってください
Please make me feel good.
チンチン気持ちよくしてください
That looks really tight, Manko.
すごいきつそうだよ、マンコウ
There are a lot of them.
つぼつぼ入ってる
Hut, Chin Chin.
ふっといよ、チンチン
Please slowly pull out and stab me, Kuro-chan.
ゆっくり抜き刺ししてください、黒ちゃん
Even the eyes are all different.
目元も全部違う
Bloody nose, this.
血の鼻、これ
Please sit up.
体を起こしてください
Please move on your own.
自分で動いてください
Please put your dick next to my face.
顔の横にチンコやってください
While sucking.
しゃぶりながら
It's so cute.
すごい可愛いじゃん
It's all full of dicks.
全部チンチンだらけだね
both above and below
上も下も
hey.
ね
Kuro-chan follows from below.
黒 ちゃん下からついて
It looks really cute.
すごい可愛いようだ
Make a perverted face.
変態な顔して
Just imagine it.
そのままイメージしてみ
Now show me this for yourself.
これで自分で見せて
It's a hard one.
硬いの刺さってるね
More Grigris.
もっとグリグリいっぱい
Please move your hips a little.
腰ちょっと動かしてください
Kuro-chan, please follow me from below.
黒 ちゃん下からついてください
Kuro-chan, please wake up already.
黒ちゃんもう起きてください
Please spread your legs.
足がばって広げてください
That's tough, Maneko.
きついね、マネコ
This one is more crispy
こっちの方がパンパンだ
hey.
ね
Please go up like this.
この まま上がってください
Please panpan.
パンパンしてください
hands behind your back.
手が後ろについて
Please spread it out as much as you can.
思いっきりがばって広げてください
It's so erotic.
すごいエロいよ
Kuro-chan, please come faster.
黒ちゃんもっと早くついてください
Faster.
もっと早く
Be patient with your back.
背に我慢ね
Please move more.
もっと動かしてください
Please take off your clothes, Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん脱いでください
Please put this chimp in here.
こっちのチンプを入れてください
Same pose again.
もう一度同じポーズです
once again.
もう一度
Please include this one too.
こっちも入れてください
please show me.
見せてください
This dick feels good too
こっちのチンチも気持ちいいで
Sho?
しょ?
It's moving, you can't stop.
動 くね、やめちゃダメだよ
Please put your hands behind your back.
手を後ろにしてください
Please follow me from below.
下からついてください
Please hold your hips with your hands.
腰もっと手で持ってください
Kuro-chan, please hold my ass with your hands.
黒ちゃん、ここはケツを手で持ってください
Please lift it up.
持ち上げてください
From below.
下から
Let's do it before.
前にしよう
Kuro-chan in the background
黒ちゃん、バックに
Please do so.
して ください
keep your ass quiet
ケツは静かにして
please.
ください
Please insert your chinpok mic.
チ ンポークマイク入れてください
About to reach the roots.
根元つくくらい
It's hitting me hard.
ぶっ刺さっているよ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Kuro-chan, hurry up.
黒ちゃんもっと早く
Please turn to the side.
横を向いてください
Kuro-chan, Taro-chan.
黒 ちゃん、太郎ちゃん
A very erotic face.
すごいエロい顔
big
大きく
It's getting worse.
な ってきたよ
Taro-chan, please follow me from behind.
太郎ちゃん、後ろからついてください
Please be normal.
正常してください
It's so ticking.
すごいカチカチ
Please come quickly.
早くついてください
please show me.
見せてください
Kuro-chan, please give it your all.
黒ちゃん、思いっきり出してください
Please let it all out.
全部出してください
Please endure to the limit.
限界まで耐えてください
Looks like it's coming in.
入ってきそう
Don't sleep yet.
まだ寝ちゃダメ
Did you put out a lot?
いっぱい出した?
please show me.
見せてください
There are a lot of pressure points.
ツボツボ入っているよ
Please follow me as hard as you can.
思いっきりついてください
amazing.
すごい
Don't go back to sleep.
また寝ちゃダメ
Taro-chan, please give it all out.
太郎ちゃん、全部出してください
Did you put out a lot?
いっぱい出した?
Please follow me from inside.
中からついてください
Please get up.
起 き上がってください
It got dirty with Sakura-chan's manjul.
桜ちゃんのマンジュルで汚れちゃった
Clean the two hips.
2つの腰をきれいにしてください
Come all the way
奥まできれ
Did you make it?
い にできた?
Yeah.
うん
How was your day?
今日どうだった?
Sandy for the first time.
初めてのサンディー
I was nervous because it was my first time.
初めてだったから緊張したけど
it was fun.
楽 しかった
楽しかった
Sakura-chan was so cute today too.
桜ちゃん今日もすんげえ可愛かったよ
I got to see a new side.
新たな一面を見れました
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Let's play again.
また遊ぼうね